geographia.com 2014-06-29

# Geographia - Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

Geographia.com, part of InterKnowledge Corp., is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. The following outlines our privacy and data protection policy. 

Other websites you may access via Geographia.com have different privacy policies and are not subject to this privacy policy. We recommend that you read the privacy statement of each such website to find out how they protect your personal information. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here.](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html)

When you visit the site, we also collect web site usage information and information about your computer and internet connection, including your computer's IP address, the type and version of browser and operating system you use, your internet domain and, if you arrived at Geographia.com via a link from another website, the URL of the linking page. We may on occasion utilize cookies.

A cookie is a small file which is placed on the user's hard drive during an Geographia.com visit. This file allows the user to move quickly and easily around our site. It is used to identify returning users and to identify subscribers and registrants.  
We use this information to find out what site features are most popular so that we can develop Geographia.com based on our analysis of people’s usage. We also use cookies and the information we collect to show you relevant content and advertising. 

This information is used to understand how better to format and arrange our website.

The results of all such research and analysis is presented as anonymous or aggregated information and can not reveal any personal facts about individuals. 

You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Geographia features or services may not function properly without cookies. 

**Information sharing**  
We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances: 

1\. We have your consent.   
We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

2\. We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of InterKnowledge, its users or the public. 

**Advertisements**  
Geographia.com sometimes uses third party providers to deliver the advertisements that are placed within the site. These providers may note some of the pages you visit on our site through the use of pixel tags (also called "clear gifs"). In the course of serving advertisements to this site, These providers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your computer on behalf of Geographia.com in order to bring to you more relevant information and in order to make sure that you do not receive the same advertisement many times in the same session. 

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the top of the page. Prior versions of this Privacy Policy will be kept in an archive for you to view.

**AFRICA   ASIA   CARIBBEAN   EUROPE  
LATIN AMERICA**  **[HOME](http://www.geographia.com/)**
